

Åke Persson

Age: 45

 ${\bf Nationality} \colon {\rm Swedish}$

 ${\bf Email:\ hello@akepersson.com}$

BACKGROUND

I'm an autodidact Full Stack Developer and Systems Engineer driven by technological challenges who started programming at a very young age. I worked in a variety of IT roles in different companies both private and govern-

ment in Sweden, Switzerland, Netherlands and USA.

EXPERIENCE

- 2021/11-Present Utopia Music AG (Stockholm/Sweden) Senior Backend Go developer.
- 2019/08-2021/08 FUGA Music (Amsterdam/Netherlands) SRE Team Lead responsible for Support, Infrastructure and Operations. Maintain and support On-Premise, Cloud Infrastructure and CI/CD tooling around it using Docker, Terraform and Kubernetes. Development of automation and tooling in Go.
- 2018/11–2019/06 Garden Leave Garden Leave during non-compete spent traveling in Europe and Asia.
- 2016/02-2018/11 IMC Financial Markets (Chicago/USA)
 Developer / System Engineer with focus on micro-service tooling for Infrastructure automation written in Go.
- 2013/06-2016/01 IMC Financial Markets (Amsterdam/Netherlands)
 Head of IT responsible for Support and Operations.
 Developer / System Engineer with focus on Infrastructure automation written in Ruby, Python and Go.
- 2009/06–2013/05 IMC Financial Markets (Zug/Switzerland) System Engineer / Developer with focus on Infrastructure automation written in Perl, Ruby and Python.
- 2006/12-2009/05 Bwin Games AB (Stockholm/Sweden)
 MySQL Database Administrator/ SAN Storage Specialist
 Largest online sports betting company in Europe. I worked for the online Poker division former Pokerroom.com.
- 03/2006-12/2006 RedBridge AB, (Stockholm/ Sweden)
 Linux consultant
 RedBridge is a consultancy with focus on Linux.
- RedBridge is a consultancy with focus on Linux.
- 2001/10-2006/04 ProAct AB (Stockholm/Sweden)
 Support specialist/ Consultant
 Specialist for Backup software Legato Networker and Unix/ Linux consulting.
- 2000/02-2001/10 Stockholm Vatten AB (Stockholm/Sweden) Application specialist
 - Maintenance and development for an in-house Water Plant monitoring software built in C and TCL/TK using Solaris and MySQL as infrastructure.
- 1997–2000/02 Support/ Unix Engineer, Stockholm Vatten AB (Stockholm/Sweden)

CIVIL SERVICE

• 1995/11–1997/01 Support Technician Marinens Krigshögskola (Marine Warfare Academy)

EDUCATION

• 1993-1995 Civil Economy Thomas Gymnasiet

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Swedish Native English Native

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Go	Expert (recent)
JavaScript/ Angular	Intermediate (recent)
HTML/ CSS/ SCSS/ Bootstrap	Intermediate (recent)
Bash	Expert (recent)
Python	Intermediate
Perl	Expert
C	Intermediate

PLATFORMS

Linux	Expert (recent)
Solaris	Intermediate
FreeBSD	Intermediate
Windows	Intermediate

REFERENCES

Upon Request.

RESOURCES

- $\bullet \ \ \text{LinkedIn} \ (https://www.linkedin.com/in/ake-persson)$
- GitHub (https://github.com/ake-persson)
 CodersRank (https://profile.codersrank.io/user/mickep76)